Models were the bait for BLACKMAIL!
The Shakedown is a crime, drama film directed by John Lemont.
Augie comes out of prison and finds his old vice racket has been taken
over by the sinister Gollar, so he dreams up a new scam.
Augie Cortona, played by Terence Morgan.
Mildred Eyde, played by Hazel Court.
Jessel Brown, played by Donald Pleasence.
David Spettigue, played by Bill Owen.
Jarvis, played by Robert Beatty.
Gollar, played by Harry H. Corbett.
The Shakedown (also known as The Naked Mirror) is a 1959 British crime-drama film directed
by John Lemont, starring Terence Morgan, Hazel Court, and Donald Pleasence.
It was written by Lemont and Leigh Vance.
A ruthless crook runs a blackmail operation, falls for an
undercover cop, and is murdered by one of his victims.
The tone is emotional.